# Mikhail Medovnik Frontend Developer

## **Contact**

#### E-mail:

medovnikfl@gmail.com

#### Web site

https://medovnikportfolio.netlify.app/

#### **GitHub**

https://github.com/gitMike23

#### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mikhail-medovnik/

# **Professional Summary**

As a frontend developer with over 2 years of experience, I have honed my skills in Javascript, React.js, Next.js and Typescript to deliver exceptional results. My passion for crafting seamless user experiences drives me to constantly push the boundaries of what's possible, while my attention to detail ensures that every project is delivered to the highest standards.

# **Work Experience**

07/2022 - pres.

### Align Technology, Yerevan, Armenia

• Frontend Developer

As a frontend developer I responsible for:

- building a web site with React.js, Next.js and Contentful;
- creating UI components using React and Typescript;
- covering the code with unit test (Jest, React testing library);

10/2020 - 07/2022

### Auriga Inc., Rostov-on-Don, Russia

Software engineer.

As a software engineer I worked on several projects:

- In the first one, I was responsible for migration of educational content of our client from one platform to Docebo using API's and backend endpoints. Our team developed an educational platform for doctors.
- In the second one, I was focused on frontend development where I developed UI components with React and Typescript for a bunch of new websites for the client.

10/2019 - 10/2020

#### Frontend Developer, Self employed, Russia

At that time I had part-time cooperation with local web studios, creating layouts for them using HTML, CSS (as well as SCSS, Bootstrap etc.) and Javascript.

#### Education

09/2014 - 06/2016

# Diplomatic Academy of the Ministry of Foreign Affairs of the Russian Federation, Moscow

Master in foreign affairs and politics.

Graduated with Honours.

2009 - 2014

## Don State Technical University, Rostov-on-Don

- B2

Bachelor of International Economics

## Languages

Spanish

English — B2

Russain — Native